(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-03T09:40:08.306197",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
いらっしゃいませ。
Welcome.
火威青 生誕3Dライブ2025へ、ようこそ。
Welcome to Hiodoshi Ao's Birthday 3D Live 2025!
はいよろこんで
With pleasure,
あなたがたのため
for all of you.
はいすり潰して
Crushing myself away
あなたがたのため
for all of you.
日々を生き延びては 稼いだ金じゃ生きてったって
Surviving each day on earned money just to get by,
いやいやで生き延びては 殻からついに立って
surviving reluctantly and finally standing on my own.
はいよろこんで あなたがたのため
With pleasure, for all of you,
できることなら できるとこまで
if I can, as far as I can go!
もう一歩踏み出して やんなこと思い出して
Take one more step forward, recall what stressed you out,
地獄オーケストラ奏でる ブンブンブン
and let the hellish orchestra play, boom boom boom!
もう一歩踏み出して やんなこと思い出して
Take one more step forward, recall what stressed you out,
なんらせ、きみの三から六マス トントンとんすすす とんすとん
whatever it is, advance 3 to 6 squares, step by step!
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス 踊れ
Barely-making-it dance, barely-making-it dance, dance!
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス もっと習って
Barely-making-it dance, barely-making-it dance, learn more!
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス 踊れ
Barely-making-it dance, barely-making-it dance, dance!
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス もっと習って
Barely-making-it dance, barely-making-it dance, learn more!
ならせ、きみの病の街を
Ring out across your town of illness,
散々、笑える他人の日にを
laughing scornfully at others' days,
散々、無茶な正義の超人たちを
all those absurd, self-righteous superheroes,
ならせ、きみの三から六マス トントンとんすすす とんすとん
ring them out across 3 to 6 squares, step by step!
怒りだしても 優しさが勝つ
Even if anger flares, kindness wins out,
あなたの...
your...
ためこんだフラストレーション
All that bottled-up frustration
パッと解放するマスターベーション
Released all at once like masturbation
どうしたの皆さんファーストデート
What's wrong, everyone on a first date?
みたいに緊張してるマスカレード
Acting as tense as a masquerade
ポーカーフェイスの裏側でも
Even behind your poker face
いけない欲求渦巻いてそう
Forbidden desires seem to be swirling
パンクしそうならぶちまけろ
If you're about to burst, let it out
気持ちいいことしよう
Let's do something that feels good
one shot
錠剤? 液体?
Liquid? Powder?
はっきりしない実体
An ambiguous substance
それは気体か固体?
Is it gas or is it solid?
聞きたいか答え?
Want to hear the answer?
言いたいと絶えずのたまうキミの期待に応え
To answer your endless expectations,
砕いて割いて巻いてって
Break it, shatter it, wrap it up,
焚いて吸って吐いてもう
Smoke it, inhale it, exhale it,
まして炙っても打っても得られない快感
An incomparable high, no matter how you take it,
たまらず give some move
Unfailing, give some move
耳から体内に入る
Entering from your ears into your body
脳内を蝕むポイズン
A poison eating away at your brain
再生するたび息吹き返す
Every time it plays, it catches your breath anew
お前の価値観ひっくり返すよ!
Overturning your worldview, yo!
いつだってグルービーに君臨する
Ruling over the groove anytime
世界の中心 yeah!
The center of the world, yeah!
ハマっちまったら終身刑
Once you're hooked, it's a life sentence
その drug の名は music
The name of that drug is music
高層ビルの谷間から海の向こう
From the valley of skyscrapers beyond the sea
蔓延する sex & drugs & rock & roll
Spreading sex & drugs & rock & roll
調教済みのブタ共は声上げろ
All you trained pigs, raise your voices!
超越する sex & drugs & rock & roll
Transcending sex & drugs & rock & roll
とっくのとうに外れたブレーキ
A sudden, broken brake,
逆らえない本能
An unstoppable instinct
crystal meth も purple haze も
Crystal meth and purple haze, too
場末の安女郎も
Even local cheap girls are fine
無くても平気 シラフでもクレイジー
Sober or crazy, it doesn't matter
タンテとマイクロフォンよこせ
Bring me the tattered microphone
合法的ないき方を心得よ
Obtain the legal way to fly
気持ちいいことしよう
Let's do something that feels good
one shot
花びら大回転さ枯れちまうくらい
Spinning petals into a grand revolution
体を重ねて fly
Overlap bodies and fly
ヌードの夜踊る乙女の美貌
The beauty of a maiden dancing in a naked night
未だ懲りずに sing a song 恋の理想
Singing songs without a care, the ideal of love
後遺症残りそうな骨折れ損
Leaving fractures and lingering trauma behind
寄り添いちゃ突き放す氷の微笑み
Snuggling close, a chilling, icy smile
ウブなふりして遊ばれよう
Play dumb and let's have fun
気持ちいいことしよう one shot!
Let's do something that feels good, one shot!
インアウト インインアウト
In out, in in out
タイトなループでヒィヒィ言わす
Crying "hee hee" on a tight loop
高嶺の花様お慕いしておりますだから押し倒して乗ります
Yearning for a high-status flower girl
なんせ魅力は満点 めちゃエロロマンス
What charm, full points, a messy ecchi nonsense
濡らしたるビッチアステオシアンクラシック sorry
A soaked bitch ass, calling you classic, sorry
その不安もわかるけど one more chance
I understand that anxiety, but one more chance
いつもはぐらかしてぶら下げて来る
Always coming around, fuzzy and dangling
ファム・ファタールの名は music
The name of the starter is music
高層ビルの谷間から海の向こう
From the valley of skyscrapers beyond the sea
蔓延する sex & drugs & rock & roll
Spreading sex & drugs & rock & roll
調教済みのブタ共は声上げろ
All you trained pigs, raise your voices!
超越する sex & drugs & rock & roll
Transcending sex & drugs & rock & roll
とっくのとうに外れたブレーキ 逆らえない本能
A sudden, broken brake, an unstoppable instinct
crystal meth も purple haze も
Crystal meth and purple haze, too
場末の安女郎も
Even local cheap girls are fine
無くても平気 シラフでもクレイジー タンテとマイクロフォンよこせ
Sober or crazy, bring me the microphone
合法的ないき方を心得よ 気持ちいいことしよう
Obtain the legal way to fly, let's do something that feels good
巻いて焚いて吸って吐いて
Wrap it, burn it, inhale it, exhale it
炙って打っておっかないぜ
Roast it, hit it, there's nothing to fear
酔っ払って抱いて
Intoxicated, holding you close
寄せでやめてよしで縁がないぜ
Pushing away, stopping, ending it—we have no ties
洒脱でなくて小汚くて土臭くて品がないぜ
Unpolished, grubby, earthy, and classless
みたいな輩はこれで飛べ again
If you're like that, fly again with this
巻いて焚いて吸って吐いて
Wrap it, burn it, inhale it, exhale it
炙って打っておっかないぜ
Roast it, hit it, there's nothing to fear
酔っ払って抱いて
Intoxicated, holding you close
寄せでやめてよしで縁がないぜ
Pushing away, stopping, ending it—we have no ties
洒脱でなくて小汚くて土臭くて品がないぜ
Unpolished, grubby, earthy, and classless
ろくにrollもできねえなら
If you can't even roll properly,
ヒップにホップで飛びじまえばいい
It's fine to just fly away with hip-hop
高層ビルの谷間から海の向こう
From the valley of skyscrapers beyond the sea
蔓延する sex & drugs & rock & roll
Spreading sex & drugs & rock & roll
調教済みのブタ共は声上げろ
All you trained pigs, raise your voices!
超越する sex & drugs & rock & roll
Transcending sex & drugs & rock & roll
とっくのとうに外れたブレーキ 逆らえない本能
A sudden, broken brake, an unstoppable instinct
crystal meth も purple haze も
Crystal meth and purple haze, too
場末の安女郎も
Even local cheap girls are fine
無くても平気 シラフでもクレイジー タンテとマイクロフォンよこせ
Sober or crazy, bring me the microphone
合法的ないき方を心得よ 気持ちいいことしよう
Obtain the legal way to fly, let's do something that feels good
巻いて焚いて吸って吐いて
Wrap it, burn it, inhale it, exhale it
炙って打っておっかないぜ
Roast it, hit it, there's nothing to fear
酔っ払って抱いて
Intoxicated, holding you close
寄せでやめてよしで縁がないぜ
Pushing away, stopping, ending it—we have no ties
洒脱でなくて小汚くて土臭くて品がないぜ
Unpolished, grubby, earthy, and classless
みたいな輩はこれで飛べ again
If you're like that, fly again with this
巻いて焚いて吸って吐いて
Wrap it, burn it, inhale it, exhale it
炙って打っておっかないぜ
Roast it, hit it, there's nothing to fear
酔っ払って抱いて
Intoxicated, holding you close
寄せでやめてよしで縁がないぜ
Pushing away, stopping, ending it—we have no ties
洒脱でなくて小汚くて土臭くて品がないぜ
Unpolished, grubby, earthy, and classless
気持ちいいことしよう
Let's do something that feels good
はーい！
Hii!
ということで、誕生日だー！
So, it's my birthday!
自己紹介させていただきます。
Let me introduce myself.
えー、可愛い女の子かと思った？じゃじゃん、青くんでした！
Did you think I was a cute girl? Ta-da, it was Ao-kun!
ホロライブデバイスリグロスのボイス担当、火威青です。
I'm Hiodoshi Ao, voice lead for Hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS.
今日は僕の3D生誕ライブに遊びに来てくれてどうもありがとう！
Thank you so much for coming to my 3D birthday live today!
え、ハッシュタグは、こちらハッシュタグ火威青生誕3Dライブ2025、こちらでスクショとかたくさん撮って僕のかっこいい顔をぱしゃぱしゃぱしゃぱしゃして、たくさんポストしてくださいね！
The hashtag is hashtag Hiodoshi Ao Birthday 3D Live 2025.
Please take lots of screenshots and post them!
わーい！
Yay!
ということで、1曲目は、え、はい、喜んでそのままで、合法的高方飛び方のすすめを歌わせていただきました。
So, for the first song, I gladly sang
"Recommended Way to Legally Fly High."
いや、言いたいことは分かってる。なんか、
Well, I know what you want to say.
あ、踊るとかじゃないんだ。ここなんだって思ったと思います。
You probably thought, "Oh, it's not dancing,
it's right here."
え、そうです！
Yep, that's right!
ここです！いっぱいここの、ここの写真をいっぱい撮って、いっぱいポストしてください！
Right here! Take lots of pictures right here
and post them everywhere!
お？なんか誰か来た！
Oh? Looks like someone's here!
こんにちは！
Hello!
おじゃましまーす！
Excuse us!
とがみん、小鳥遊！小さくなっちゃって。ちっちゃくなっちゃった！
Togamin, Takanashi! You got so small.
You shrank!
お誕生日おめでとう！おめでとう！
Happy birthday! Congratulations!
あ、ちょっと来てくださった3人のプリンセスの自己紹介をしていただけましょうか？
Could the three princesses who came here
please introduce themselves?
じゃあ、身長小さい順からどうぞ。
Alright, starting from the shortest, please go ahead.
はい、一番ちっちゃいリジック所属のURS-No.1005、とがのもしばす！お願いします！
Yes, the smallest, belonging to ReDict,
URS-No.1005, Togami Nen! Please!
あ、とがちゃんこれです。ちょっと大きいし！次ね、こっちかな。
Ah, Togachan, this is it. I'm bigger!
Next up, maybe this way.
こっちは、えっと、ネオポルテ3期生、悪魔教のコンコンアリアです。よろしくお願いします！
And this is Neo-Porte 3rd generation,
Koncon Aria of the Demon Cult. Nice to meet you!
はい、いいね！
Yeah, nice!
はい、2時3時、いやの所属のキョラメロコでございます。よろしくお願いいたします。
And yes, I am Kyo Ramelloco
belonging to Nijisanji. Nice to meet you.
一番でっかい女でーす！やったー！
I'm the biggest woman! Yay!
一番でっかいの私たちよ！何言ってる？
We're the biggest ones! What are you saying?
まあ、一番でっかいのは僕らだから、揉めるな！変わらないでしょ！
Well, since we're the biggest, don't argue!
It won't change!
え、ちょっと来てくれてありがとう。今日はあれですか？僕を指名しに来てくれたんですか？
Thanks for coming. Did you guys come
to nominate me today?
そうだよ！かっこいいって言えるって聞いて。写真撮りに来た！
That's right! We heard we could call you cool.
We came to take pictures!
可愛い青くん撮りに来たい！かっこいい青くん撮りに来てくれた！
We came to take cute Ao-kun photos!
We came to take cool Ao-kun photos!
まあかっこいいかっこ、かっこいい過去語り、うん、そう、かっこいい過去真実、ありがとう。
Well, cool past stories, yep, that's right,
cool past truth, thanks.
あ、可愛い！かっこいいよ！間違ってるね、はい。
Ah, cute! You're cool! You're wrong, yep.
と言うことで、じゃ、せっかくだからお写真撮っていきましょうよ。
With that said, since we have the chance,
let's take some photos.
一杯用のポーズしてよ、任せて、ポーズ取るのだけ生業にして生きてきたんだから。
Give us lots of poses. Leave it to me,
posing is my sole profession.
青くん、大はしゃぎにより大幅カット！※フルは後日公開！？
[Title: Ao-kun got too excited, massive cut!
*Full version coming later!?]
どうでした？でもなんか噂によるとみんなはさ、みんなもさ、僕のこの写真用の枠書いてきてくれたって聞いたんだけど。
How was it? But rumor has it that everyone
drew frames for my photos.
どんなの？じゃあまず、
What kind? Well first,
あ、なんじゃこれ！これ誰のなのかな？
Ah, what is this?! Whose is this?
え、これ誰の？この文字見たらわかる。
Eh, whose is this? You can tell from the letters.
え、すごい！これなんか
Eh, amazing! This is like...
アップ、アップを見せたくて。
I wanted to show a close-up.
あ、可愛い！かっこいいな、かっこいいな、かっこいい、かっこいい。これしてていいね。
Ah, cute! So cool, so cool, cool, cool.
Doing this is nice.
眉毛下がるやつちょっとえっち、えっちだな。かっこいいかっこいい、眉毛下がるのがいいな。
The one with drooping eyebrows is a bit lewd.
Cool, cool, drooping eyebrows is nice.
青くんキラキラできないの？あっ、出せるよ！
Can't Ao-kun sparkle? Ah, I can bring it out!
めっちゃ！オーラ出してオーラ、オーラ！イケメンオーラ！
Super! Put out aura, aura!
Handsome aura!
うわ、出た！出た！いい、いい、いい！
Whoa, it came out! Good, good, good!
あ、可愛い！かっこいい！かっこいい！めっっちゃいい！これめっちゃナンバーワン！
Ah, cute! Cool! Cool!
Super good! This is super number one!
かっこいい！これ普通に欲しい欲しい欲しい！送って！撮ってる撮ってる撮ってる！
Cool! I want this normally, want it!
Send it! You're taking pictures!
これ最高の写真撮れたよ！ポストしなきゃ！
We took the best picture! We have to post it!
いやすがなんばーわん！え、嬉しい！ありがとう！ナンバーワンふんすあなたにやったー！ナンバーワンスきた！
Iyasuga Number One! Eh, I'm happy!
Thank you! Number one Funsu to you, yay!
昏昏アリア 作
[Title: Created by Koncon Aria]
あーん♡ え、待って、やば！はい！コンコンアリアが描いてきました！
"Ah-n♡" Eh, wait, no way!
Koncon Aria drew this!
うわ、これやば！プロ、プロすごいやんこれ！これ今回言ってあげてよこれ！
Whoa, this is insane! Pro, so amazing!
Tell him this time!
あーん。お誕生日おめでとう、ケーキ！あーん♡
Aah... Happy birthday, cake! Aah♡
お前が本体だよもう！
You're the main body!
うれしい！
Yay!
いっぱい食べてね！
Eat up a lot!
おいしい！
Delicious!
いや、これ天才といえる。これ天才だよな。
Man, this is genius. Absolutely genius.
ねぇ、動き動きやめてね。右見えてるから。
Hey, stop moving! I can see the right side.
青くん、おて♡
Ao-kun, paw♡
青くん、おてしてごらん、おて。
Ao-kun, give me your paw. Go on, paw.
私におてしてごらん？
Give me your paw, okay?
これ... これって何？
What... What is this?
でもお手っぽい！お手でもいいし、顔のせてもいいし。
It looks like a paw! Or a face is fine too.
顔も乗るんだ。
It fits on your face too.
顔はいいか、これ。やりよし、やりよし、やりよし！
Is the face okay? Do it, do it, do it!
ちょっと悲しい顔をしたいけどね。悲しい気持ちだけどね、今。
I want to make a sad face, though.
深い悲しみな顔をしてる。
You've got a deeply sorrowful look.
あ、それそれそれ！それが見たかった！それが見たかった！
Ah, that's what I wanted to see!
なんだこれ？
What is this?!
青くんはやっぱ、大きい犬みたいなとこあるから。
Ao-kun has that big dog vibe, after all.
違和感。おてしてごらんって。
No way. "Give me your paw," it says.
いや、大きいイケメンだけどね。
Well, you're a big bishounen, though.
この状態で、もう1枚見せてほしいな。
I want to see one more in this state.
じゃあこの状態からの、私もう1個持ってきたの。プレゼント持ってきたの。
So from this state, I brought another present.
すごい。降りていただかないのきたけどね。
Amazing. Though I came here without getting down.
あ、じゃあちょっと、あ、だから、お誕生日おめでとうだから。だからうんち、だからうんち、これうんち...
Since it's a birthday, poop, this poop...
うんちでしょ、これ。
It's poop, isn't it?
これうんち！これうんち好きでしょ、あんた。
This is poop! You like poop, don't you?
なんんで？あんたずっとうんちうんち言ってんだから！
Why? You keep going on about poop!
あ、これ一番きれいなうんちのことでしょ？
Is this about the cleanest kind of poop?
あ、そうそう。これ一番きれいなうんち持ってきた今日。2025年で一番きれいだなと思って。
I brought the cleanest poop of 2025 today.
まだ始まってばっかなんだよ！
The year has barely begun!
うわ、すごい。手に乗せて持ってきた。ちょっとこれキラキラいらないだろ、ここキラキラ。
Whoa, amazing. The sparkles are unnecessary.
オーラ、オーラ消して。
Turn off the aura.
朝うんち光ってっから、私それのせいで光らせてきた今日。
My morning poop glowed, so I made it glow.
そっかそっかそっか。じゃあ2枚目、いらないです。
I see. Then I don't need the second one.
これいらないです。それ欲しかった！それ欲しかったやつ！それめちゃくちゃいい！
I wanted that! That's the one I wanted!
何これ何これ。ちょっと困らせたかった。
What is this? I wanted to put you in a bind.
顔がいいな、おい！
You've got a great face, hey!
いや、顔がいいな。ほんとにかっこいいわ。え、ほんと？あ、よかった。喜んでくれてよかった。
Man, your face is great. Glad you're happy.
うれしい、うれしい！
Yay, I'm so happy!
じゃあこんぐ、まだあるんじゃないの？
Konk, aren't there still more?
え、そう。私もあるんで。そうなの？え、見たい見たい。こんぐ先生はちょっと信用度高いよ。
Oh, I have one too. Konk-sensei is trusted.
がんばりました。最後にみよう、それ。
I did my best. Let's look at that last.
え、待って、これめちゃくちゃかっこいいじゃん！
Wait, this is super cool!
すでにハマってるじゃん。なんだこれ。
You're already into it. What is this?
え、知ってた？もしかしてね。
Eh, did you know? Maybe?
え、すごいすごい。被りに来てたじゃん！
Whoa, amazing! You came wearing it!
青くん、ちなみに下にちっちゃいカマキリいるから、それは手に乗せる用だよ。
There's a little mantis for your hand, Ao-kun.
なんて？なんでちょっと芸が細かいんだよ。
What? Why is the gag so detailed?
ここ、ここかな。そうそうそう、いい、いい、いい。
Right here, maybe? Yeah, good, good.
え、さっきのさ、メロコさんのうんちと...本当だ！これうんちと同じじゃん！
Wait, Meroco-chan's poop... It's the same!
これ合わせたわけじゃないんだ。うん、これ、こいつが出てきてから。
You didn't coordinate this? Ever since this guy came out.
あれ、え、こいつよりでけえうんちだったけどな、完全に。
Wait, that poop was way bigger than this guy.
写真同士で嬉しいです。ねえ。
Taking photos together makes me happy. Right?
僕もうれしかったよ。ありがとう。
I was happy too. Thank you.
本当？え、なんか疲れてない？大丈夫？
Really? Are you tired? Are you okay?
大丈夫、大丈夫。疲れてないよ、全然。
I'm fine, I'm fine. Not tired at all.
いや、寝るな、寝るな！起きろ起きろ！
Hey, don't sleep! Wake up!
信じてたのに。まだゲストがいるんだぞ、ここに。
And I trusted you. There are still guests here!
いや絶対、いつかかしがえししてやるからな！
I'll definitely get you back someday!
君たちが3Dになった暁には、僕もいたずらを仕掛ける。
The moment you guys become 3D, I'll prank you too.
おお、怖いな。しかもあれじゃない、せっかくだからさ、みんなでさ。
Ooh, scary. Since we're at it, everyone...
今日いいないピザ屋のメンメンも合わせて、みんなでいつか3Dになったらなんか歌って踊ろうね。
Let's sing and dance together in 3D someday.
やろう、やろう！
Let's do it!
夢叶えよう、それみんなで。
Let's make that dream come true together.
じゃあ最後にみんなで写真撮ろっか。オーケー、やった！
Let's take a group photo. Okay, yay!
いしょっと。
Here we go.
写真撮れる？撮れるの？え？
Can we take a photo? Can we?
ひっくり返ってない？これ大丈夫？
Is it not upside down? Is this okay?
よしよしよしよし。え、なにこれ？
There, there. What is this?
おいう、ごっつあん。え？
Hey, thanks a lot. Eh?
なにこれ？知らない知らない。
What is this? I don't know this.
アリナのパネルあ、待って。これは知らないやつ。
Alina's panel... wait, this is new to me.
え、いい、よろしい、よろしいんですか？え、よろしいのこれ？すご！
Is this okay? Are you sure? Amazing!
よし！メロコさん！あ、メロコさんが倒れることだった。
Alright! Meroco-san was supposed to fall over.
私、メロコさん反対だよ！メロコさん反対にして。
Wait, Meroco-san is the wrong way! Turn her around.
やばいやばいママ様にごめんなさいってね。
Oh no, apologize to Mama-sama.
いいね、写真撮ろ。
Nice, let's take a photo.
え、やばいじゃん！身長差あるな！
Whoa, there's a height difference!
身長差いいよね、やっぱね。あるだろ、がよ。
Height differences are great, after all.
あ、いいんじゃない？ なんか いい写真なんじゃない？
Ah, isn't it good? Like, isn't it a nice photo?
コンビってかな？ コンビ、コンビね
A combination, you mean? Combination, yeah.
お団子の髪の毛がね、シュガクリムがちゃんの団子食べてる
Dango hair... Sugar Cream-chan is eating dango.
そのへん ちっちゃいからね
Right around there, cause it's super small, you see.
言いません、言います
I won't say it. I won't say it.
ということで、このこれを記念撮影して 最後にしましょうか
And so... let's take a commemorative photo of this and make it the last thing!
ということで、じゃあ聞いていいですか？ お誕生日おめでとうって言ってもらっていいですか？
So... Can I ask you to say "Happy Birthday"?
はい、じゃあせーの
Then, ready, go!
お誕生日！ おめでとう！ おめでとう！
Happy Birthday! Congratulations!
ありがとう！ 来てくれてありがとう！ バイバーイ！
Thank you! Thanks for coming! Bye-bye!
ありがとう！ バイバーイ！ ありがとう！ バイバーイ！
Thank you! Bye-bye! Thank you! Bye-bye!
ふう。 あれ？
Phew. Huh?
マリンちゃん！
Marine-chan!
おい！
What?
んだこの店は？
Wh- What is this shop?
え、見てみてみて、綺麗でしょ？作ってもらった
Eh, look, look! Isn't it pretty? I had it made.
あんさー、マリーは客か？
Oh, really? Is Marine a customer?
違うよ！
No way!
なあ、なんだか全部営業だったんだね
Hey... So it was all just work, huh?
なに言ってんだ、なに言ってんだ、もう！
What are you talking about, seriously!
本庄マリン、ちょっと落ち着け
Honshou Marine, calm down.
ほら、マリンちゃん、君のための薔薇だよ。死に晒せ！
Here, Marine-chan. This is a rose for you. Drop dead!
あー！薔薇が！
Ah, the rose!
青くん
Ao-kun.
はい
Yes.
見て？
Look?
あ、な、なんてこと持ってきんだこれ
Wh- What kind of thing did you bring here?!
ほら、可愛いしょ？
Look, cute right?
可愛くない
Not cute.
見ててね、行くよ
Watch, here I go.
はっ！わあ！
Ha! Wow!
はい、これ5秒後のお前の姿
Here, your appearance 5 seconds later.
ひゃあ！
Kyaa!
さあ、森へお帰り！
Now, back to the forest!
あ！カメムシ！
A stink bug!
今日がお前の命日
Today is your death anniversary!
きゅー！天罰！
Kyaa! Divine punishment!
ふざけんな！ そもそもお前が！
Are you kidding me?! You started it!
なんで誕生日なんだよ！
Why is it a birthday?!
はぁ？ ごめん。 おめでとう！
Ha? Sorry! Congratulations!
ふざけんな、お前！ なにが誕生日だ！
Are you kidding me?! What birthday?!
落ち着けって、マリンちゃん！
Calm down, Marine-chan!
スキヨ キライ ワカンナイ キライ
I like you, dislike you, I don't know, dislike you
スキ ダ イガイ アリエナイ スキ ダ
I like you, it couldn't be anything else, I like you
スキト キライ ワカンナイ 止まれない スキキライ
I like and dislike, I don't know, I can't stop, like and dislike
もう あいつ の ココク って やつ 頭 の 中 グルグル と 回る
Already, that guy's confession spins around and around in my head
回る いつの 告白 って やつ 頭 の 中 ぐるぐると回る
Spinning, that confession from back then, spinning around and around in my head
スキ キライ 真ん中 は ある の ? せんだい られる 二作
I wonder what lies between? Do I really have to choose one?
そう 返事 は 決まってる はずさ ウェディング
Yes, the answer should already be decided: a wedding
そう ビジョン は 完璧
Yes, the vision is perfect
そうだ 住む の は 松濤 あたりが いい な
That's right, living around Shoto would be nice
だって 待って なんて だって 14歳 です
Wait, wait, why? Because we're 14 years old!
付き合う とか 好きだ 話聞いて バカ ノードガード だぜ
Going out, or "I like you", listen to me you idiot with no guard
スキ が 多い の 恋して みたいわ ふわふわと
You've got so many weak spots, I want to fall in love, all fluffy
ミルク と パンダ は シロクマ で 世界 が はズ ムノ
Milk and panda make a polar bear, making the world bounce
スキ ト キライ ワカンナイ キライ でも スキ
I like and dislike, I don't know, dislike, but I like
ミルク と パンダ は シロクマ で 世界 が はずむ の
Milk and panda make a polar bear, and the world bounces!
スキ ト キライ ワカンナイ キライ でも スキ
I like, dislike, I don't know, dislike, but I like
レインボー クオーツ 変えりみし 欲しがっていた やつ 眺める
Rainbow quartz from the shop window you were staring at
数学 の 問題 だ けど それ は 気 に し ない で って いう か あまり 好き じゃ ない タイプ ゆえ に
It's a math problem, but don't worry about that. Or rather, since it's not my usual type
反動 でしょ う か すこし 急 に 優しく なんか さ れ た から
Maybe it's a reaction, since you suddenly acted so nice to me
グラ ついて どう よ おっと てぐっと そっと ぬいて 冷静 に なっ て
I'm shaking, what should I do? Pulling back smoothly, staying calm
間違い なく 理屈 ぬき で スキ ノー プロブレム 僕 を 信じ て
Without a doubt, ignoring logic, I like you, no problem, believe in me
君 に 火 を 点け た ゆらゆら と 燃え て
You lit a fire in me, burning flickeringly
ほら 君 に 火 を 点け た ゆらゆら と 燃え て ハイ に なる バイ の マニア 愛し て いる ん だ よく わから ない けど
Hey, you lit a fire in me, burning flickeringly, getting high, loving you so much, though I don't quite understand
スキヨ キライ ワカンナイ キライ
I like you, I hate you, I don't know, I hate you
スキ ダ イガイ アリエナイ スキ ダ！
There's no way it's anything other than love—I love you!
スキ ト キライ ワカンナイ
Love or hate, I just don't know
止まれない スキキライ
This love-hate won't stop
もう！ あいつの告白ってやつ
Hey! That guy's sudden confession
頭の中 グルグルと回る
Makes my head spin around and around
スキ キライ 真ん中は あるの？
Is there a middle ground between love and hate?
迫られる 二者択一
Forced to choose between two options
もう 返事は決まっているはずさ
Well then, the answer is already decided
「wedding」そうヴィジョンは完璧！
"Wedding"—yes, that vision is flawless!
（そうだな、住むのは松濤あたりが良いな ♪）
(That's right, living around Shoto would be nice ♪)
子供は3人かな (^_^)
Maybe we'll have three kids (^_^)
だって 待って 何で？
Hey, wait, why?
だって 14歳ですー… ですよ？
Because I'm 14 years old... aren't you?
「付き合う とか…」
"Going out, or..."
「好きだ」
"I love you"
恋してみたいわ ふわふわ と
I want to fall in love, feeling so fluffy
校長 ハゲ の スピーチ に スマイル
Smiling at the bald principal's speech
ミルク と パンダ は シロクマ で
Turning milk and pandas into polar bears
世界 が はずむ の ♪
Making the world bounce with joy ♪
スキ ト キライ ワカンナイ ah…
Love or hate, I don't know, ah...
キライ でも スキ？
Hate, but still love?
「ホイ！！」
"Hey!"
「エッ！？」
"Eh!?"
レインボー クオーツ 帰り道
Rainbow quartz on the way home
欲しがってたやつ
The one you wanted so badly
眺める君を僕は視ていた
I was watching you gaze at it
通学路反対だけど
Even though it's the opposite way from school
てぇーか！ あんまりスキじゃないタイプ
I mean! Not really my type
ゆえにう～ん… 反応でしょうか
Hence, hmm... is this a reaction?
（そっか、急に優しくなんかされたから…）
(I see, since you suddenly acted so nice...)
グラつついて動揺
Wavering and flustered
タってグッとそっとヌいて
Stepping up, pulling close, slipping away
冷静になってみても
Even if I try to stay calm
間違いなく！
Without a doubt!
いなくぅ？
Without a...?
理屈ヌキでスキ
I like you, no logic needed
ノープロブレム 僕を信じて
No problem, trust me
ほーらっ
See ~
君 に 火 を 点け た ゆらゆら と
Lit a small flame inside you, flickering
燃え て high に なる パイロ マニア
Burning up high, a pyromaniac
「愛しているんだ！」
"I love you!"
よく 分からない けど おそらく 正解
I don't really know, but it's probably right
やだ な 染め られ そう…
Oh no, I'm about to be dyed...
知って シマタ 優しさ
I've come to know your kindness
時 に ヘンタイ でも
Even though you're sometimes a pervert
スキ に ソメラ レ テカ…
Being dyed in love...
恋してみたいわ ギラギラと
I want to fall in love, intensely
パンダが寝てちゃツマラナイ
It's boring if the panda is sleeping
愛して出して水を与えて
Pouring out love, giving water
初めて育つ の
That's how it first grows
ぶつかる二人同時 の スキ
Our feelings of love colliding at once
絡み合うフロマージュ
Intertwining fromage
キライさえ裏表
Even "hate" is just the flip side
僕ら今恋してる
We are in love right now
スキヨ キライ ワカッテレル… スキヨ
I like you, I hate you, I understand... I like you
恥ずかしい？
Embarrassed?
ちょっと、ちょっとね。
A little bit.
青くんいくよ、せーの、お誕生日おめでとう！やったー！
Ao-kun, here we go! Ready, happy birthday! Yay!
やったー！
Yay!
おめでとう！ありがとうございます！
Happy birthday! Thank you so much!
素敵な、初めての青くんのバースデーライブですね！
It's Ao-kun's wonderful first birthday live!
そうです！うー！
That's right! Woo!
初めての、すごいよ、見て！
Look at this, it's amazing!
えー、すごいステージ！これすごい見て、ほら、サイリウムも！
Whoa, what an amazing stage! Look at the glow sticks!
え、これ店だよな？
Wait, this is a club, right?
おい、もう一回やるのかこのやつ。
Hey, are we doing this skit again?
やめてそのコント！はい、え、喧嘩コントでした。
Stop that skit! Right, uh, that was an arguing skit.
はい、でも、でも？
Yeah, but, but?
僕はやっぱり、この初めての3Dライブでマリンちゃんと一緒に歌って踊れたこと、マジ一生の宝物ってわけ！
I really... getting to sing and dance together with Marine-chan in this first 3D live is truly a treasure for a lifetime!
マジ一生の宝物ってわけ！
Truly a treasure for a lifetime!
どうも！お疲れです！イエーイ！
Hello! Good work! Yay!
やだ！やだね！一人でやってるマジで！捨てろよ！
No way! No way, doing it all alone for real! Throw it away!
人の誕生日のMCで暴れ散らして、おりまっし散らしてるですね。
Causing a ruckus and scattering chaos during someone's birthday MC.
えー、ということで。あ、もう邪魔ですか？あ、いいえ。このままここに住もうと思ってたんですけど。
Uh, so anyway. Ah, am I in the way? Ah, no. I was thinking of just living here.
あ、いいね。そうしたいことはやまやまなんだけど、いていいんだよね、ここに。
Ah, that's nice. I'd love to do that, but it's okay to stay here, right?
何か見られてまずいものでも？ふふ、そんなのない。あ、そんなのない、ぽぽぽーん。
Anything you wouldn't want seen? Haha, nothing like that. Ah, pop-pop-pon.
また一緒にこうやって歌って踊ってくれるから！
Because you'll sing and dance with me like this again!
誕生日おめでとう！おめでとう！
Happy birthday! Congratulations!
おなか空いた。
I'm hungry.
さて、次のプリンセスはっと、あ！mio先輩！
Now, as for the next princess... Ah, Mio-senpai!
青くーん！
Ao-kun!
来てくれてうれしー！
I'm so glad you could come!
呼んでくれてありがとう！うわー、元気だな！
Thanks for inviting me! Wow, you have so much energy!
僕も隣社に引っ越そうかなつって。
I was thinking of moving into the neighboring company.
え、何この素敵空間？なんかちょっとムーディーな感じ。
Eh, what is this wonderful space? It feels a bit moody.
ムーディーでしょう。これね、なんと見てくださいよ。じゃん！僕のお店！
It is moody, isn't it? Look at this, everyone. Ta-da! My shop!
すごい！すごいいね、めちゃ豪華だ！はい、お邪魔しちゃってと。
Amazing! That's so nice, super luxurious! Right, excuse me for dropping in.
なんやかんやこうやって二人で喋るのってあんまないかも。
Talking like this just the two of us doesn't happen very often.
だってなんかいつも。
Because usually...
あれ、もう一人？あ、あれ？
Huh, another person? Ah, huh?
か、かっこいい願望のもう一人が！イロハも見てるかー！イロハ先輩！寿司を！寿司をー！
T-The other person of our cool desires! Is Iroha watching too?! Iroha-senpai! Sushi! Sushi!
いや、今回は二人ですけど。いつかはね、3人でも何かやりたいですね。
Well, it's just the two of us this time, but someday we'd love to do something with all three.
今度は一緒にやろうな、今度は！歌お、歌おう！よろしくお願いします！
Let's do it together next time! Let's sing, let's sing! Looking forward to it!
あ、そういえば青くん誕生日おめでとう！ありがとうございます。あ、忘れてた。
Oh, by the way, happy birthday Ao-kun! Thank you very much. Ah, I forgot.
あははっ！
Ahaha!
あ、そうだった。
Oh, that's right.
そうだよ。
Yeah, that's right.
誕生日だから呼んだんだよ、今日ここに。
It's your birthday, so we invited you.
あ、そうなんです。
Ah, that's right.
やった！
Yay!
兄弟、やったやった！
Brother, yay, yay, yay!
やったー！
Yay!
あのさ、ちょっと気になってること聞いていい？
By the way, can I ask you something I'm curious about?
もちろんですよ。
Of course.
何でも聞いてください。
Ask me anything.
え？
Huh?
足元にいるの何？
What's that at your feet?
あ。
Ah.
あ、寄生ガイさん。
Ah, Kiseigai-san.
え？
Huh?
あんなでっかいのが家から家出たってこと？
Why did such a big thing come out of the house?
いやいやいや違う違う違う。
No, no, no, no.
曽我さんワゴンは？
Is it a Soga-san wagon?
家に出たのはもう本当こん、こんなんだったけど、
What came out of the house was really like this...
うん。
un...
あれは、こうちょ表現されたカメムシってこと？
That was a stuffed version of the Kiseigai.
そうです。スタッフさんの悪ふざけですね。
That's right, it's the staff's bad joke.
ええ。
Yeah.
「いらなーい」って言ったけど、
They said, "We don't need it."
うん。
un.
なんか、スタッフの姉さんが「え？
Some staff member said, "Huh?
せっかく作ったけど、本当にこんないらないの？」って言われて、
You went to all the trouble to make it, but really?
作ってんじゃん。
Are you making it?
は？
Huh?
「いらなーい」って言っちゃった。
"I don't need it," I said.
「いらなーい」って言っちゃった！
You said you don't need it!
言っちゃった。
I said it.
言い掛けだ！
You jinxed it!
カメジカケ？
Kamemushi-jigake?
カメジ、カメジカケ？
Kamemushi... Kamemushi-jigake?
うん。
Yeah.
なんかかっこいいなそれ。
Sounds cool, though.
カメジカケだね。
Kamemushi-jigake, huh?
はい。
Right.
え、なんかさ、うちはさ、
Hey, you know, our place...
は！
Ha.
こうやって、こう青くんの、なんて言うんだろ？
how should I say it?
ホス、ホストみたいな感じの企画をやったりしてるよね？
Host-like kind of project, they do that, right?
そうですね、一応やらせていただきますね。
That's right, we do, we do.
ええ。
Yeah.
それでなんかこう、接客を...
So, like, connection...
を受けたことがうちはないから、お店に行ったことないから
Uchi hasn't experienced that, never been to a store.
あ。
Ah.
なるほど。
I see.
うん。
Yeah.
でもこちら、実はですね、
But actually, here...
はい。
Right.
ホストではなく、
It's not a host club,
普通のバーなんですね。
it's just a normal bar.
あ、そうなの？
Ah, is that so?
ええ、違うんだ。
That's right.
一番最初のホストクラブでやってこうかなって思ったけど、
I thought we'd do it at the very first host club,
うん。
un.
なんかホロメンの先輩方、リグロス含め向いてないなって思って。
Somehow, I felt like the seniors of Holomen, including Ligros, didn't really fit in...
違います違います違いますね。
Ah, that's true, that's true.
受ける側としても向いてなかっってこと？
You mean it didn't fit from the receiving end?
なんか
Something like...
あ、ちょっ、ちょっと空気が違うなってんで、
Ah, a little...
普通に飲み屋にしました。ええ。
ordinary drinking it is.
あ、そうなんだ。
Ah, is that so?
ええ。せっかくだからなんかそういう接客みたいなの
Yeah, since it's a special occasion, something like that service...
え？
Huh?
欲しいですよね？
You want it, right?
やってくれるんですか？
Can you do it for me?
もちろんですよ。
Of course.
ホストクラブっぽいことではないですけど、僕あれできます。
It's not really like a host club, but I can do this.
え、どれ？
Which one?
イリュージョンができます。
Illusion.
え？イリュージョン？
Eh? Illusion?
はい。見ますか。
Yeah, let's see.
みたーい！
I want to see!
やってやって！
Do it, do it!
え？
Huh?
何系？何系？
What kind? What kind?
トランプ系とかベロベロ系？
Trump trick or Vero-Vero trick?
これ。
This.
おー！
Oh!
クスカラバラが！
Kusukara rose!
かっこいー！
Cool!
かっこいー！いえーい！
Cool! Yay!
それ口から出す時にさ、口の中ずたずたんなんなかった？大丈夫？
When you take it out of your mouth, was your mouth all sloppy?
意外と、うん。
Surprisingly...
あの、取っちゃえばいける。
you can just take it out.
あ、大丈夫。
Ah, is that so?
ええ、トゲトゲ取っちゃえば大丈夫。
If you take it out thorns and all, it's fine.
トゲ意外とポリって取れるんだ。
You can take the thorns off cleanly?
あー、そっかそっか。
Ah, I see, I see.
ポリって取って、加えればオッケー。
If you take it off cleanly and add it, it's fine.
オッケーオッケーね。
Okay, okay, then.
で、やっぱり僕たち、
And, やっぱり僕たち
このよにかっこいい二人。
this cool duo.
おー。
Oh.
かっこいいコンボですからね。
We're a cool combo, after all.
そう。
So.
うん。
Un.
かっこいい歌。
A cool song.
お！
Oh!
歌いたい！
I want to sing!
かっこいい歌？
A cool song?
かっこいい歌、二人で？
A cool song, together?
今日はいろは先輩はいませんが、
Iroha-senpai isn't here today,
僕たち二人で、
but just the two of us...
かっこいい歌を歌って、
singing a cool song,
僕も王様。
I'm also a king.
ミオ先輩も王様。
Mio-senpai is also a king.
うちも？
And me?
そう。
So,
二人で
the two of us...
かっこよくなろうと思います。
want to get cooler!
おー！
Oh!
歌うぞー！
Let's sing!
いぇーい！
Yay!
やったー！うちもかっこいいやつ歌うぞー！
Yay! We'll sing a cool song too!
やったー！
Yay!
王様って二人でもいいものなのかな？まいいか。
Kings, well, is it fine for there to be two?
まあ、国の数だけあるんでね。
Well, there are as many as there are countries.
伝説の朝に誓った言葉
The words we pledged on that morning of legend,
分かち合う声に奇跡を照らせ
Let the miracle illuminate our shared voice.
革命をLet's shout
Revolution, let's shout!
風の舞う光の空　ふきぬける残響
The wind dances through the sky of light, and the echo blows through.
この右手とこの左手
This right hand and this left hand,
何を求める？
What do they wish for?
革命のデュアリズム　さあ始めよう
Revolution's dualism - now, let's begin!
以心伝心　生の咆哮　届いていますか？
Does the telepathic roar of life reach where you are?
ついてこい　夢の果て
Follow me to the end of the dream!
その日　君はジャッジメントする
When that day comes, you will pass the judgement.
革命をLet's shout
Revolution, let's shout!
キスみたいにクラックした
Like a kiss, it has cracked into my system,
色褪せないドリーム
a forever-colorful dream.
未来へのドアはコインのトスさ
The door to the future is the toss of a coin.
虹のかかる　見たことない
Crossing the rainbow as you've never seen,
覚醒のデュアリズム　さあ飛び込もう
Awakening's dualism - now, let's fly in!
百花繚乱　鳴る流動感
Emerging legends, howling impulse,
火花を散らして
send the sparks flying!
どこまで行けるのか？
How far can we go?
覚醒のデュアリズム　さあ始めよう
Awakening's dualism - now, let's begin!
ついてこい　夢の果て
Follow me to the end of the dream!
その日　君はジャッジメントする
When that day comes, you will pass the judgement.
革命をLet's shout
Revolution, let's shout!
キスみたいにクラックした
Like a kiss, it has cracked into my system,
色褪せないドリーム
a forever-colorful dream.
未来へのドアはコインのトスさ
The door to the future is the toss of a coin.
虹のかかる　見たことない
Crossing the rainbow as you've never seen,
覚醒のデュアリズム　さあ飛び込もう
Awakening's dualism - now, let's fly in!
伝説の朝に誓った言葉
The words we pledged on that morning of legend
痛みを押して 目を護り 闇を信じ 生きろとゆう
Pushing through pain, guarding our eyes, believing in the dark
未来へのドアは コインのトスさ 残酷を選べ 暁の君
The door to the future is a coin toss. Choose cruelty, O dawn's child.
虹の架かる見たことない 絶景のフライト教えてやるよ
I'll show you a flight to a stunning view across an unseen rainbow.
覚醒のデュアリズムさ ああ飛び込もう 百花繚乱共鳴する衝動
Awakening's dualism—now, let's dive in! A riot of flowers, a resounding impulse.
火花を散らして 胸のブレイブを叩く鼓動 どこまでいけるのか
Sparks flying, the beating pulse that strikes bravery in our chests—how far can we go?
変わらないナニカで なんどうくちづけした そして君は まったくいにで逢う
With something unchanging, how many times have we kissed? And then you meet once again...
Just trust my heart Just feel my heart ...hold you
Just trust my heart, just feel my heart...
誇り高き愛の結晶 握りしめたら 迎えにゆくから
Once you clasp the crystal of proud love, I'll come to meet you.
刹那から一生さえ すべて見せてきた 君へのlove song
From a fleeting moment to a lifetime, showing it all—a love song to you.
Break out! 鎖ちぎって 独立せよ
Break out! Tear apart the chains and declare your independence!
Just trust my heart Just feel my heart
誇り高き愛の結晶 握りしめたら 迎えにゆくから
Once you clasp the crystal of proud love, I'll come to meet you.
刹那から一生さえ すべて見せてきた
From a fleeting moment to a lifetime, showing it all—
君へのlove song Break out! 鎖ちぎって 独立せよ
a love song to you. Break out! Tear apart the chains and declare your independence!
変わらないナニカで なんどうくちづけした そして君は まったくいにで逢う
With something unchanging, how many times have we kissed? And then you meet once again...
Just trust my heart Just feel my heart ...hold you 誇り高き愛の結晶
Just trust my heart, just feel my heart...
Break out! 鎖ちぎって 独立せよ
Break out! Tear apart the chains and declare your independence!
異次元新星の方向 届いて 今すぐ 踵返の愛がでしょう
Heading toward a new dimension, reach out right now, and let love echo.
ついてこい夢の果て どんなロードだって いつかは街にあうその日
Follow me to the end of dreams, no matter the road, until that day we meet in the city.
君はジャッジメントする 革命を･･･ 革命を･･･
You will pass judgment—Revolution... Revolution...
革命を･･･ 革命を･･･
Revolution... Revolution...
夢をかなえてドラえもん
Make my dream come true, Doraemon
心の中いつもいつも描いている 夢をのせた自分だけの世界地図
In my heart, always imagining a world map of my very own with dreams loaded on it
(タケコプター!)
(Take-copter!)
空を飛んで時間を超えて遠い国でも ドアを開けてほら行きたいよ今すぐ
Flying through the sky, crossing time, even to faraway lands, open the door and let's go right now!
(どこでもドア!)
(Anywhere Door!)
大人になったら忘れてしまうのかな?
When I become an adult, will I forget?
そんな時には思い出してみよう Shalalalala 僕の心にいつでもかがやく夢
At times like that, let's remember. Shalalalala, a dream that always shines in my heart
ドラえもん そのポケットでかなえさせてね
Doraemon, please make it come true in that pocket of yours
Shalalalalala 歌をうたおうみんなでさあ手をつないで ドラえもん 世界中に夢をそうあふれさせて
Shalalalalala, let's sing a song together, holding hands. Doraemon, let's fill the world with dreams!
大人になったら忘れちゃうのかな
When I become an adult, will I forget?
そんな時には思い出してみよう
At times like that, let's remember
Shalalalalala 僕の心にいつでもかがやく夢
Shalalalalala, a dream that always shines in my heart
ドラえもん そのポケットでかなえさせてね
Doraemon, please make it come true in that pocket of yours
Shalalalalala 歌をうたおうみんなでさあ手をつないで
Shalalalalala, let's sing a song together, holding hands
ドラえもん 世界中に夢をそうあふれさせて
Doraemon, let's fill the world with dreams!
(タイムマシン!)
(Time machine!)
やりたいこと行きたい場所見つけたら 迷わないで靴を履いて出かけよう
If you find something you want to do, a place you want to go, don't hesitate, put on your shoes and go out!
(タイムマシン!)
(Time machine!)
大丈夫さひとりじゃない僕がいるから
It's okay, you're not alone, I'm here
キラキラ輝く宝物探そうよ
Let's search for the shining treasures
(四次元ポケット!)
(Four-dimensional pocket!)
道に迷っても泣かないでいいよ 秘密の道具で助けてあげるよ
Even if you get lost on the road, don't worry, I'll help you with a secret tool
やりたいこと行きたい場所見つけたら
If you find something you want to do, a place you want to go
迷わないで靴を履いて出かけよう
Don't hesitate, put on your shoes and go out
(どこでもドア!)
(Anywhere Door!)
大丈夫さひとりじゃない僕がいるから
It's okay, you're not alone, I'm here
キラキラ輝く宝物探そうよ
Let's search for the shining treasures
(四次元ポケット!)
(Four-dimensional pocket!)
道に迷っても泣かないでいいよ
Even if you get lost on the road, don't worry
秘密の道具で助けてあげるよ
I'll help you with a secret tool
Shalalalalala 口笛吹いて高らかに歩き出そう
Shalalalalala, whistle a tune and let's go for a walk
ドラえもん あの街まで届けばいいね
Doraemon, it's fine if you just reach that town
Shalalalalala 僕たちの未来夢がいっぱいあふれてる
Shalalalalala, our future is overflowing with dreams
ドラえもん 君がいればみんなが笑顔になる
Doraemon, if you're here, everyone will smile
Shalalalalala 口笛吹いて高らかに歩き出そう
Shalalalalala, whistle a tune and let's go for a walk
ドラえもん あの街まで届けばいいね
Doraemon, it's fine if you just reach that town
Shalalalalala 僕たちの未来夢がいっぱいあふれてる
Shalalalalala, our future is overflowing with dreams
ドラえもん 君がいればみんなが笑顔になる
Doraemon, if you're here, everyone will smile
シャララララ
Shalalalala
僕らの未来
Our future
夢がいっぱい あふれてるよ
is overflowing with dreams.
ドラえもん 君がいれば みんな
Doraemon, if you're here, everyone
笑顔になる
becomes full of smiles.
大人になっても きっと忘れない
Even when we grow up, we'll never forget
大切な想い
our precious feelings.
いつまでも ずっと
Forever and ever.
シャララララ 僕の心に
Shalalalala, in my heart
いつまでもかがやく夢
a dream that shines forever.
ドラえもん そのポケットで かなえさせてね
Doraemon, let me make it come true with your pocket.
シャララララ 歌をうたおう みんなでさあ手をつないで
Shalalalala, let's sing a song, everyone holding hands together.
ドラえもん 世界中に 夢を そうあふれさせて
Doraemon, let dreams overflow throughout the world.
シャララララ 歌をうたおう みんなでさあ手をつないで
Shalalalala, let's sing a song, everyone holding hands together.
つまらないデイイズもう散々ね!
Boring days are already over!
奇跡願っているだけの人生活
A life just wishing for miracles
watch me do...
呪術秘中トリック無しのマジック
Magic with no tricks or secrets
I wanna be free! だってまだ始まりだし
I wanna be free! Because I'm still at the start
(The party ain’t started)
Heyタクシー ちょっと宇宙まで
Hey taxi, take me to space for a bit
秒針は音を立てて夜を急かす魔ものような
The second hand ticks loudly, urging the night like a monster
人生は一瞬にして溶ける魔法
Life is a magic that melts away in an instant
それなら駆け抜けて思い通り!
If so, run through it just as you wish!
おしゃまな馬車飛び乗ってDriving
Jump on the playful carriage and start driving
あたしは大変身メイクアップ!
I'm in the middle of a great transformation, make-up!
我儘のままに華麗に注意
Be careful not to get caught up in selfishness
洒落た街でDancing
Dancing in a stylish city
さようならグッバイ劣等感
Goodbye, inferiority complex
何時は喝采クラップオーディエンス 皆々御詠和あれ!
Someday, applause from the audience. Everyone, join in!
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA 混濁がっても仕様がない
Bibbidi bobbidi boowa, even if it's chaotic there's no other way
グラスシューズで踊るtonight
Dancing in glass shoes tonight
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA 今夜に明日などない
Bibbidi bobbidi boowa, there's no tomorrow tonight
ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょう?
So those who dance freely win, right?
Dance! ラララリホ
Dance! La la la li ho
どんな問題も解は一つ
Every problem has only one solution
白紙も正解も間違いも愛する
Love blank papers, correct answers, and mistakes
本当のあたしの理想
My true ideal
なんだか世界は限界の気がして
The world seems to have limits I can feel
ただただ安心じゃあ心配
Just being safe is worrying
今すぐjumpin jumpin out
Jumpin out right now
chitty chitty bang bang
chitty bang bang
唯々諾々に危機感抱く日々いに
In days when I feel an urgent crisis
ぎりぎり爆発気味
Explosive feelings are at their limit
たった今発散してしまおうか
Should I let it all out now?
まだまだビビビ弾け身に乱射
Still firing away skillfully
一発じゃあ撃ち足りないわ
One shot is not enough
ついに導き出した君にアンサー
Finally, I found the answer
灰になるまで踊っていよう
Dance until it turns to ash
おしゃまな馬車飛び乗ってDriving
Jump on the playful carriage and start driving
あたしは大変身メイクアップ!
I'm in the middle of a great transformation, make-up!
我儘のままに華麗に注意
Be careful not to get caught up in selfishness
洒落た街でDancing
Dancing in a stylish city
さようならグッバイ劣等感
Goodbye, inferiority complex
何時は喝采クラップオーディエンス 皆々御詠和あれ!
Someday, applause from the audience. Everyone, join in!
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA 混濁がっても仕様がない
Bibbidi bobbidi boowa, even if it's chaotic there's no other way
グラスシューズで踊るtonight
Dancing in glass shoes tonight
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA 今夜に明日などない
Bibbidi bobbidi boowa, there's no tomorrow tonight
ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょう?
So those who dance freely win, right?
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA 混濁がっても仕様がない
Bibbidi bobbidi boowa, even if it's chaotic there's no other way
グラスシューズで踊るtonight
Dancing in glass shoes tonight
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA 今夜に明日などない
Bibbidi bobbidi boowa, there's no tomorrow tonight
ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょう?
So those who dance freely win, right?
はあ 誕生日楽しかった!
Haah, my birthday was so fun!
ゲストもたくさん来てくれて最高の誕生日だ!
So many guests came, it's the best birthday ever!
よっしゃ!
Alright!
お誕生日おめでとう!
Happy birthday!
最高じゃん！おめでとう！
This is the best! Congratulations!
おめでとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Congratulations! Thank you so much!
あ、あ、じゃあ自己紹介するか。
Ah, ah, then shall we introduce ourselves?
うん。
Yeah.
行くぞ。
Let's go.
D.J.度トップ、ウィ・アー、リーダーズ！
D.J. Top, we are Leaders!
全然違うんだよ！
That's completely wrong!
え、なんで工藤じゃないの？
Huh, why isn't it Kudo?
俺らがいつこれが揃うんだよ！
When are we ever going to get this right?!
せっかくなので自己紹介をお願いいたします。
Since we're at it, please introduce yourselves.
はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes!
じゃあ、かなでから行きます！
Then, Kanade will go first!
え、たまたま友達に誘われたライブ会場に来てみたら、あれ、青さんの誕生日ライブでした！
Um, I happened to come to a live venue my friend invited me to, and lo and behold, it was Ao-san's birthday live!
おめでとう！ラッキーガール！イエイ！
Congratulations! Lucky girl! Yay!
そして？はーい！
And next? Hii!
どうも、可愛いポジティブジーニアス一條莉々華だよ！家でゲームをしてて、あー、このイケメン、画面から出てこないかなって画面を割ったらここに繋がっちゃったみたいな。わあ！
Hello, I'm the cute, positive genius Ichijou Ririka! I was playing games at home, thinking, 'Ah, won't this handsome guy come out of the screen?' and when I smashed the screen, I ended up connected right here! Wow!
え、これ画面割れたやつ？え、これ褒められてるの？
Huh, is this the screen-breaking one? Huh, am I being praised here?
まいっか、まいっか。そして？はい！
Oh well, oh well. And next? Yes!
はい、儒烏風亭もは、全然罰当たりじゃないごろすの賑やか系VTuberこと儒烏風亭ラデでございます！
Yes, Juufuutei... wait, Juufuutei Raden, the bustling VTuber who is totally not committing sacrilege!
えっと、えっと、シャンパンの伝票が、あ、こちらになりますので、よろしくお願いし、あ、もうカゴで置いときます。
Um, um, the champagne bill is... ah, here it is, so thank you... ah, I'll just leave it in the basket.
いや、シャンパン下ろしたの、ラデちゃんが。
No, Raden-chan is the one who ordered the champagne.
まいっか。あ、そし て？
Oh well. Ah, and next?
はい！
Yes!
ぷぷぷ、儒烏風亭の番長、轟京子初めれっち。
Pupupu, Juufuutei's bancho, Todoroki Kyoko here, nice to meet you.
なんかポーズ可愛いな。
Somehow that pose is cute.
え、今？え、ずっとやってる？あ、そうなの？今初めて知っ たわ。
Huh, right now? Huh, you've been doing it the whole time? Ah, is that so? I just found out now.
お披露目からずっとやってる。やってるぜ！
I've been doing it ever since the reveal. I sure am!
いや、こんにちは、この流れが ちょっと、もう分かんなくなっ てきちゃった。
Man, hello, I'm starting to lose track of this flow.
口から生まれた轟京子初めれっち。
Todoroki Kyoko, born from the mouth, nice to meet you.
ありがとうって言ってくれてありがとう！ありがとう！
Thank you for saying thank you! Thank you!
ガラスの靴やな！
That's a glass slipper!
そういうことね！ちょ、ちょ、ちょ、
Is that what it means! Wait, wait, wait,
てかステージめちゃいいやん！
I mean, this stage is so nice!
どうしようこれ！
What should we do about this!
ブルーファイアーってこと？そう！
You mean Blue Fire? That's right!
あのなんか、お座敷とかで使ったあれの、大丈夫か？大丈夫か？
That thing we used at the tatami room and stuff, is it okay? Is it okay?
お座敷思い出すね！
It reminds you of the tatami room!
お座敷ちょっと思い出さないで欲しいけどね、それは！
I'd rather you didn't remind us of the tatami room, though!
間違いない！お座敷だよ、これ！あ、いいでしょ、その椅子！
No doubt! It's a tatami room, this! Ah, isn't it nice, that chair!
え？え？え？
Eh? Eh? Eh?
壊してる！壊してる！壊してる！
It's breaking! It's breaking! It's breaking!
やばい！よいからだじゃん！お座敷だよ！
Oh no! What a good body! It's a tatami room!
やばい！お座敷だよ！
Oh no! It's a tatami room!
え、だって、でもお酒はあるよ！
Eh, wait, but there is alcohol!
お酒飲んでいいよ！誰か止めて！誰か止めて！
You can drink alcohol! Someone stop her! Someone stop her!
お酒美味しい！
Alcohol is delicious!
あ、あ、あ、シャンパンタワー、あ、やってないよ！やってないよ！
Ah, ah, ah, champagne tower, ah, we haven't done it! We haven't done it!
やってない、やってないって！言ってるだろ！
We haven't, we haven't! I'm telling you we haven't!
やりたい放題だよ！やりたい放題してんだよ！やりすぎだよ！
They're doing whatever they want! They're going too far!
バイオレンス！
Violence!
イエーイ！波乱万丈なこと、波乱万丈なこと、波乱万丈なこと
Yay! A tumultuous thing, a tumultuous thing, a tumultuous thing...
そんなことやろうとしてない！
We're not trying to do something like that!
え、この、この子、え、えい！えい！えい！えい！
Eh, this, this child, eh, ei! ei! ei! ei!
ラデちゃん、ごめん。
Raden-chan, sorry.
ラデちゃん、ごめん。それもみんなやってる。
Raden-chan, sorry. Everyone is doing that too.
あ…
Ah...
て！
Te!
それもやってる！なんだこれ！
She's doing that too! What is this!
いや、ちょっと待って。
No, wait a minute.
でも、でも番長はね、番長はもう何もやらないから。信じてるよ、番長。
But, but Bancho, Bancho won't do anything anymore. I believe in you, Bancho.
さすがにね、あーん。
Naturally, right? Ah...
やあ！あー！これ高いんだよ！見て！めっちゃ綺麗なんだね！
Yay! Ah! This is expensive! Look! It's so pretty!
大暴れだ、大暴れだ！
Rampage, rampage!
やべ！やべ！
Oh crap! Oh crap!
おい！青くんが壊したぞ！
Hey! Ao-kun broke it!
やりたかったことなのに！あー！そう、この後もまだまだあったのに！
Even though it was what I wanted to do! Ah! There was still more after this!
もう終わりだね！終わりじゃない！
It's already over! It's not over!
お前たち全員、この後ステージ直せよ！
All of you, fix the stage after this!
大法違反やねん、危険やから。
It's a major violation, it's dangerous.
この後もステージ直すの、君たちにも手伝ってもらうからな！ええー！
You guys are going to help me fix the stage after this too! EHH?!
ということで、しょうがないなあ。
So, it can't be helped.
ちゅっ。
Chu.
なんかすごい賑やかですけれども。
It's super lively, though.
まあ、一応言うか。こんなセット際は、こりごりだー！ありがとうございましたー！
Well, I guess I'll say it. I've had enough of this kind of stage side! Thank you very much!
女々しくて 女々しくて 女々しくて 辛いよ
Unmanly, unmanly, unmanly, it's so painful
僕のことをからかったの
Did you make fun of me?
あんなに好きと言ったのに
Even though you said you loved me so much
奴のどこを気に入ったの？
What did you like about that guy?
女々しくて 女々しくて 女々しくて辛いよ
Unmanly, unmanly, unmanly and painful.
僕の事をからかったの?
Did you make fun of me?
君と手を繋ぎ踊りたい
I want to hold your hand and dance with you.
たくさんの人ごみの中で
In the middle of the crowded crowd,
君の笑顔だけが輝いて
only your smile was shining.
愛されたいねきっと見過ごした
I want to be loved, I must have overlooked
君のシグナルもう一度
your signal once again.
気まぐれかな?でも構わない
Is it fickle? But I don't care,
君と居たいから
because I want to be with you.
女々しくて 女々しくて 光を浴びて
Unmanly, unmanly, soaking in the light,
女々しくて 女々しくて 恋の歌歌って
unmanly, unmanly, singing a love song.
女々しくて 女々しくて いざ辿り着いたこの世界はもう
Unmanly, unmanly, the world I've finally reached is already
女々しくて 女々しくて 女々しくて辛いよ
unmanly, unmanly, unmanly and painful.
辛いよ
It's so painful...
今日はオトコの娘は忘れよ
Let's forget about crossdressing today.
昨日の古い悩みなど
Yesterday's old worries and such—
君は誰を?次は何と?
Who are you with? Who's next?
心を酌み交す
Sharing our hearts with one another.
本当は抱き合って眠りたい
To be honest, I want to hug and sleep,
カラカラに渇いた心を
and drench my parched heart
君の美しさで潤して
in your beauty.
恋に焦がれていつもミスをした
Yearning for love, I always made mistakes.
Yearning for love, I always made mistakes,
女心 雲の様
a woman's heart like clouds.
惚れた晴れた 狭い心が また拗ねている
Falling in love, my narrow heart is sulking again.
またねだんではいられない
I can't ask for much yet.
女々しくて 女々しくて 二人を見つめ
Unmanly, unmanly, watching the two of you,
女々しくて 女々しくて 君が笑顔で
unmanly, unmanly, with your smiling face,
女々しくて 女々しくて 奴の手物に触れたこの胸はもう
unmanly, unmanly, touching that guy's hands, this chest is already...
女々しくて 女々しくて 女々しくて辛いよ
unmanly, unmanly, unmanly and painful.
オッケーエブリバディ!
Okay, everybody!
楽しまなきゃ生きてるフォールインラブ
Gotta enjoy life, falling in love,
だけど楽しいばかりじゃアイムプライド
but it's not just fun, I'm proud.
生まれてきてごめんねレディナイト
Sorry for being born, ready tonight,
整わないけど等身大
but keeping it real.
ギターソロ、キャン・ユタカ!
Guitar solo, Can Yutaka!
愛嬌と言うかただ君が欲しい
Call it charm, I just want you;
僕の心、犬のよう
my heart is like a dog's.
だまされたってどうぞ構わない
I don't care if I'm deceived,
君と居れるなら
as long as I can be with you.
愛されたいねきっと見過ごした
I want to be loved, I must have overlooked
君のシグナルもう一度
your signal once again.
気まぐれかな?でも構わない
Is it fickle? But I don't care,
君と居たいから
because I want to be with you.
光を浴びて
Soaking in the light,
恋の歌歌って
singing a love song.
いざ辿り着いたこの世界はもう
The world I've finally reached is already...
女々しくて 女々しくて 女々しくて辛いよ
Unmanly, unmanly, unmanly and painful.
辛いよ
It's so painful...
ステージが直った…
The stage is fixed...
直っていなくても直ってるけどまあいか。
Well, even if it's not fixed, it's fixed, whatever.
次が最後の曲になります。僕の初めてのオリジナル曲です。
Next will be the final song. It's my very first original song.
聞いてください、「Club Blue Fire」。
Please listen to it, "Club Blue Fire".
久しぶり！早く君が来ないかなってずっと持ってんだんだ
Long time no see! I've been wondering when you'd come.
ようこそ、Club Blue Fireへ!
Welcome to Club Blue Fire!
お客様、さあどうぞVIPのお席へ
Dear guest, right this way to your VIP seat.
手始めにハイボールを飲み干したら始めましょう
Let's start by drinking down a highball.
足りない 足りない 酔えてない 飛び交う怒涛のシャンパンコール
Not enough, not drunk, amid the raging champagne calls.
つれない?つれない?んなこと無い 不機嫌な姫にアルコール
Unresponsive? No way, alcohol for the displeased princess!
よそ見しないで 僕を選んで 夜に溺れてしまう前に
Don't look away, choose me, before you drown in the night.
夜に溺れてしまう前に
Before we drown in the night,
疑わないで
don't doubt it,
二人抜け出そう いっそ
let's slip away together, come on!
今宵、皆Party さぁParty 踊り明かそう
Tonight, everyone Party, come on Party, let's dance the night away!
ふらついているHoneyからCalling
Calling from a wobbling Honey,
Tonight Tonight Tonight… 自問自答
Tonight Tonight Tonight... self-questioning.
この世は天国か？それとも地獄か？
Is this world heaven? Or is it hell?
正解などないんじゃない 音に乗っかってCome on!
There's no right answer, right? Ride the beat, come on!
馬鹿になっていいじゃない？
Wouldn't it be fine to act like a fool?
僕らはまだ
We're still...
足りてないって 酔えてない
not satisfied enough, not drunk enough.
Welcome to the “Blue Fire”
Welcome to the "Blue Fire"
Stop！こっからがShow time ご注目、ご清聴It’s alright？(HaHa)
Stop! From here on is showtime. Pay attention, listen up. It's alright? (HaHa)
卓越し突き刺した君のEyesから感じる嫉妬に凍る脳内
My brain freezes from the jealousy felt in your piercing, peerless eyes.
終わらない 止まないSaturday night 独占欲渦巻くホール（また）
Endless, unstopping Saturday night in a hall swirling with possessiveness (again).
燻り出す 泣き出す 暴れ出す 混乱照らしたミラーボール
Smoldering, crying out, running wild—the mirror ball illuminating the chaos.
僕の目を見てほら、手握って？
Look into my eyes, come on, hold my hand?
“出会った場所が此処だった”だけ
Just that "where we met happened to be right here."
誰にも言えない約束をしよう そっと
Let's make a promise we can tell no one, softly.
今宵、皆Party さぁParty 酔い潰れそう
Tonight, everyone Party, come on Party, we're about to pass out from drinking.
ギラついてるシャンデリア仰ぎ
Looking up at the glaring chandelier,
Tonight Tonight Tonight… 自業自得
Tonight Tonight Tonight... you reap what you sow.
天使の囁きか？悪魔の誘惑か？
An angel's whisper? Or a devil's temptation?
判断力など もう無い 本性晒しちゃってCome on!
No judgment left at all, bare your true nature, come on!
さあさあ！こちらVIP 1番テーブルにお座りの素敵な素敵な姫様から！なんと！シャンパンタワーいただきました！
Now, now! From the wonderful, wonderful princess seated at VIP Table 1! What an amazing champagne tower received!
本日の王子、青くんから姫様へ感謝の気持ちを込めてシャンパンコール送らせていただきます！
From today's prince, Ao-kun, to the princess, expressing our gratitude, we will now send you a champagne call!
今夜は！今夜は！あなたがいなけりゃ（始まない！）
Tonight! Tonight! If you're not here, (it won't start!)
では、せーので！（乾杯！）おまけに！（乾杯！）飲めない青くん（見たくない！）
Now, on three! (Cheers!) Plus! (Cheers!) Ao-kun who can't drink (I don't want to see it!)
この身果てるまで（命果てるまで）火女（ひめ）の幸せに（尽くして頂戴！）飲んで！（飲んで！）飲んで！（飲んで！）
Until this body perishes (until life perishes) for the princess's happiness (serve her to the fullest!) Drink! Drink! Drink! Drink!
座右の銘はDrinking Knight！
My motto is Drinking Knight!
泡沫の向こう側に消えた本音と
True feelings that vanished beyond the bubbles,
惚けた表情のHoney
and a vacant-looking Honey.
Tonight Tonight Tonight… 諸行無常
Tonight Tonight Tonight... everything is transient.
僕を待ち受けるは裁きか救いか？
Waiting for me is judgment or salvation?
考える必要はない
There's no need to think.
『愛してるって言ってるじゃん…！』
"I'm telling you I love you...!"
今宵、皆Party さぁParty 踊り明かそう
Tonight, everyone Party, come on Party, let's dance the night away!
ふらついているHoneyからCalling
Calling from a wobbling Honey
Tonight Tonight Tonight… 自問自答
Tonight Tonight Tonight... self-questioning
この世は天国か？それとも地獄か？
Is this world heaven? Or is it hell?
正解などないんじゃない 音に乗っかってCome on!
There's no right answer, right? Ride the beat, come on!
馬鹿になっていいじゃない？
Wouldn't it be fine to act like a fool?
僕らはまだ
We're still...
足りてないって 酔えてない
not satisfied enough, not drunk enough.
Welcome to the “Blue Fire”
Welcome to the "Blue Fire"
はーい！ありがとうございましたー！
Hii! Thank you very much!
どうでしたか？どうでしたか、どうでしたか？僕の初めてのオリジナル曲！
How was it? How was it, how was it? My very first original song!
なんとこの後アニメーションMVが出るので、サビのダンス一緒に踊ってね！めっちゃ気合い入れたMVなんで絶対見てください。
An animated MV will be released right after this, so please dance along to the chorus! I put so much passion into this MV, so you definitely have to watch it.
ということで告知があります！誕生日グッズが出るよ！どんっ！
And with that, I have an announcement! Birthday merchandise is coming out! Boom!
火威青 誕生日記念2025、1つめはこちら！
Hiodoshi Ao Birthday Celebration 2025, the first one is right here!
キミの王子様☆青くんフレームアートボード！イラストはむっしゅママにお願いしています！
"My Prince" Ao-kun Frame Art Board! The illustration was requested from Mushu-mama!
オリジナルアイドル衣装を着た僕がめっちゃかっこいいアートボードになっています！印刷もこだわっているのでぜひ見てください！
It's an art board where I look super cool wearing my original idol outfit! We were particular about the printing too, so please check it out!
2つめは こちら！青くんおしゃれランダムミニアクリルスタンドキーホルダー！
The second one is right here! Ao-kun Stylish Random Mini Acrylic Stand Keychain!
イラストは万歳寿大宴会先生にお願いしています！あのよく歌ってみたとかで依頼してる推し神絵師ですね！いろんなおべふくを…いろんなの本当にマジ最強のかっこいいのやってもらったんで！はい！
The illustration is requested from Banzai Kotobuki Daienkai-sensei! That's the oshi-kami illustrator I often commission for cover songs and stuff! They made me wear various outfits... really the strongest, coolest ones! Yes!
かっこいい！次！
So cool! Next!
キミの王子様☆青くんぬいぐるみ！衣装原案は先ほどのあのアートボードをむっしゅママにお願いしています！
"My Prince" Ao-kun Plushie! For the outfit concept, I asked Mushu-mama for the art board mentioned earlier!
ぬいぐるみデザイン原案は今回も僕がやりました！なんかめっちゃ今時っぽいぬいぐるみになってるんで、あのぜひデートに連れて行ってください！はい！
The plushie design concept was done by me this time too! It turned out to be a super modern-looking plushie, so please take it on dates with you! Yes!
次はこちら！青くんのシャンパングラス！
Next is this! Ao-kun's Champagne Glass!
僕と言ったら、やっぱりシャンパングラスだよね！僕にシャンパンを入れるつもりで、ぜひ手にいれてください！
When you think of me, it's definitely a champagne glass, right? Please get your hands on one with the intention of pouring champagne for me!
最後はこちら！ASMRボイス「ライブ終わりにキミと2人で！」
Last is this! ASMR Voice "Alone with You After the Live!"
このボイスは、今日このライブが終わった後にキミと2人で おうちデートをする、そんな内容になっています！
This voice is about having an at-home date with you just the two of us after today's live ends!
ふふっ
Heh.
風景か？次！
A view? Next!
フルセット購入特典はこちら。
Here are the full set purchase bonuses.
通常バージョンでは、箔押し複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードが特典についてきます。
The regular version comes with a foil-stamped duplicate-signed cheki bromide card.
数量限定バージョンでは、直筆サインをこうやって書くのでよろしくお願いします。
For the limited quantity version, I'll be writing my actual signature, so please look forward to it!
また、フルセット共通特典として青くんからのメッセージボイスもあります。
Also, as a common full-set bonus, there's a message voice from Ao-kun.
これは完全にアドリブで撮ったものなので、その時の気持ちを受け取ってね。
This was recorded completely unscripted, so I hope you can feel my emotions from back then.
はい、ということで。そしてタレントプレミアムグッズのフルセット特典として、
Right, with that said. And as the full-set bonus for the talent premium goods,
ホロライブタレントカードです！ 去年から発売されたホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームで使用できるカードが1枚付きます。
it's the hololive talent card! You'll get one card for the Hololive Official Card Game.
カードはホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップで購入された方のみ対象となります。
This card is only for those who purchased from the Hololive Production Official Shop.
特典につくのは、推しをアピールできるキーカード、推しホロメンカードです。
The bonus includes the key card to show off your oshi, the oshi holomen card.
カードの詳細や遊び方についてはホームページにてご確認ください！
Please check the homepage for card details and how to play!
ということで、グッズ紹介はこんな感じ。
And that's it for the goods introduction.
このあとすぐオリ曲のMV公開があります。
Right after this, the MV for my original song will be released.
面幻のアンコールライブにもぜひ遊びに来てね。
Please make sure to come play at the unlimited encore live too.
ということで、僕の3Dライブに来てくれて本当にありがとう！
So, thank you so much for coming to my 3D live!
愛してる！してる……
I love you! I do...
バイバーイ！MV絶対見てね！
Bye-bye! Make sure to watch the MV!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
今宵、皆party！ さあparty！ 踊り明かそう
Tonight, everyone party! Come on, party! Let's dance the night away
ふらついてるhoneyからcalling
Calling from a wobbly honey
tonight tonight tonight... 自問自答
Tonight, tonight, tonight... Soul-searching
この世は天国か？ それとも地獄か？
Is this world heaven? Or is it hell?
正解などないんじゃない 音に乗っかっていって come on！
There's no right answer, just ride the beat, come on!
バカになっていいじゃない？ 僕らはまだ 足りないって、酔えてない welcome to the “Blue Fire”
Isn't it fine to act a fool? We still aren't satisfied, aren't drunk enough, welcome to the "Blue Fire"